This is how I'll become.
Supreme Commander!
A hero!
This is my story!
In the dark dark,
One, one, another one, The tears of tears
I'm crying!
I'm trying to get my hope?
Oh, wow!
I've seen my dreams.
It's not as high as I can!
It's the best thing I wanted.
Welcome, ma 'am. Thank you.
Yuki. Huh?
I'm going to do the paperwork.
Wait for me outside.
Uh, sure.
So the 5th Squad's gateway is
connected all the way to Yamagata?
It was only a 20-minute
drive on the other side.
Interdimensional travel is nuts.
Thanks for waiting.
What's wrong?
Oh, yeah!
It's just nice to be
back in our home world.
We'd all burn out without a break
from work every now and then.
But time off's in short supply.
Enjoy the fresh air while you can.
Yeah.
I never really noticed till
now, but she's really pretty.
Look ahead when you walk.
Oh, sorry about that.
By the way, may I ask where we're going?
Hmm?
Yuki!
Yuki! Yuki!
Have you seen Yuki?
Yeah, he went out with the
commander for some time off earlier.
He did? Uh-huh.
Himari took them to the Yamagata Passage
while she was out on her regular patrol.
That's right.
Today is...
There was an incident at Mount Kasan,
in Oisawa, where dozens of
Shuki wandered into this world.
One of them was especially powerful.
I remember it as though it were yesterday.
It had a single horn that stuck
out from the top of its head.
So I called it the Unihorn.
All of the Shuki that crossed
over that day were wiped
out by the demon defense
force who arrived to help.
Or so I thought.
But after looking through the records,
I discovered the Unihorn managed to
escape back through the gateway into Mato.
So then the Unihorn is still alive.
I have a score to settle
with that damn Shuki.
I swear, I will destroy that thing.
And I want you to be prepared
for when that day comes.
That's what I brought
you here to talk about.
I will avenge everyone who died.
It's time for us to go back to Mato.
Wait a minute, Miss Kyouka.
Can we take a break first?
I did a little research.
This cafe is famous for its parfaits.
Mato is far more important. Check it out!
Look at that!
It's amazing, isn't it?
Fine, but make it short.
You're more assertive than
I thought you would be.
You surprise me.
Well, you enjoy sweet treats
like everyone else, don't you?
I'm just more concerned about
motto than I am about desserts.
I lost my big sister in a motto mishap a
while ago, so it's important to me too.
I totally get it.
But you'll miss your chance at vengeance
if you run yourself ragged first.
We'd burn out without a break from work.
Remember?
Persuasion is another forte of yours,
I see. Very nice. Here you are.
Let's see how good this parfait really is.
Wow, fantastic!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Just caught up in my thoughts.
Delish.
Seeing a smile on Kyoka's
face for the first
time actually brought back
memories of my sister.
Wow, it's delicious.
I took your suggestion from yesterday
and added a little bit of Yuzu citrus.
You're such a smart little cookie,
I give it a million thumbs up.
I'm so proud of you.
Keep up all of your hard work, okay, Yuki?
Boys are defined by their
skills in the kitchen.
Are you going to have any?
Oh, um, um, it's delicious.
The parfaits here really
are as good as they say.
Yeah.
A conch shell?
It's an emergency call from Mato.
A single blow of the shell
means it's not life-threatening.
But something serious is
happening nonetheless.
Break time is over.
We need to hurry back.
You want that here?
Oh, wow.
That wiped me out.
We made it back home in no time flat.
Nicely done.
I'm going to go change.
Okay.
Why don't you come with me? Huh?
So, um...
Start by helping me take these off.
Um, is this my reward from your ability?
And what the hell else
could it possibly be?
Oh yeah, that's a good point.
Hurry up. Yes, ma 'am.
Holy crap, we're deep in fetish territory.
Does that mean I'm wishing for
this kind of stuff subconsciously?
It's exactly what you think.
You damn pervert.
Welcome back, you two.
Give me the breakdown.
There was a discovery made
during today's patrols.
A crater-like formation appeared
about 21 kilometers to the south,
along with a large number of Shuki.
Hold on.
Are all of those red dots
supposed to be Shuki?
A crater, huh?
We've never seen anything like that.
They're not making any moves
to leave that area either.
It's like a nest of some kind, right?
Apologies for ruining your day off.
That's okay.
Good work.
This problem needs our attention
This is a huge undertaking
for the seventh squad.
Yeah, let's smash them all like bugs
Someone's fired up
Prepare to move out.
We'll ride in three vehicles
Right!
I count as the third vehicle?
We're going on ahead. Yuki!
He's fast.
He's just a wild animal.
It would be horrific if
any people got stuck here.
Let's clear them out.
Don't rush it.
You will wait for my signal.
It'll take the seventh squad's perfect
teamwork to eliminate all of them.
Here it goes!
Kimari! I'm on it!
If they merge, it'll be easier
than taking them down one by one.
That's our time to shine.
We'll crush the big one and call it a day.
The Shuki are tough bastards, but
their fighting style is simplistic.
Our strategy is flawless.
Once they've reshaped, we will
destroy them once and for all.
Be ready to jump into battle at any time.
Yes, ma 'am!
Huh? It's Kyoka!
Shushu!
One horn on top of its head!
It's him.
Damn it!
I'm here to join the party. It talks?
Are you some kind of monster?
Now that's not a very nice thing to say.
Be careful.
Because I have more than a sharp tongue!
Himity!
Ah, that felt great!
Well now, aren't we a tough one?
I finally found it.
That unicorn will die!
Huh, it sounds like they have
a cute little nickname for you.
That's him, the bastard who
destroyed Kyoka's hometown.
You! On the Shuki!
Who are you?
I guess you could say I'm the
Demon Defense Force's archenemy.
Amato Peach?
By the way, have you seen
my little brother anywhere?
Easy to spot.
I mean, seeing as he's
incredibly handsome.
Little brother there are
more of these things.
My little brother was
obsessed with me when
we were younger always
following me around.
Annoying, but adorable!
In spite of that, the instant he got
older, he turned into such a rabble!
But those were the fun days, because
I got to knock some manners into him!
It can talk?
Is it a Shuki? Whatever.
All that matters right now is that this
one's clearly different from the rest.
My little brother's name is...
I'm talking about my brothers!
So don't get to wrap me!
Have a snack.
I get it.
You must be their supreme commander!
My goodness!
You don't know anything
about Mato, do you?
This is a world filled with curses!
Help!
You've got a nice shuki of your
own, but it's time to say goodbye!
Huh?
This isn't Ashuki. You're...
You coward!
Don't run away from me! Miss Kyoka!
Fine, then.
I'll do exactly what you did
to all those fleeing villagers!
And tear you to pieces!
Yuki, now!
What are you doing?
They're getting away!
Shushu, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Yuki! Huh?
Heimari and Shushu, safety is priority.
We're gonna pull back now.
Yes, ma 'am!
What was I thinking?
I let my rage take over.
and it almost cost me my squad mates.
Fortunately, their wounds
are relatively minor.
They'll be fully recovered by tomorrow.
That's great news!
Anyway,
I can't believe the kind of filthy rewards
that come out of your subconscious.
Seriously, what is wrong with you?
You're disgusting.
Yeah, I know.
The demands of my inner psyche
are starting to terrify me, too.
In regards to that last battle,
I have a lot of questions and
comments to go over with you.
For starters...
I have something I want
to report to you as well.
But does it have to be
while we're like this?
I don't want to waste time.
And this reward of yours isn't
going to end anytime soon.
I'm really sorry that
the Unihorn got away.
Shushu's and Himari's
lives were more important.
I appreciate all that you did out there.
Well, you have an interesting
way of showing it. Shut up!
This is something that you
subconsciously asked for, you perverse!
Back to the Unihorn.
That humanoid writing on top of
it must be some species of Shuki.
It's crazy to think that a
Shuki could speak our language.
This news is going to
shock the entire country.
Well, speaking of that new species,
remember when I told you
about my missing big sister?
I think that thing kind of resembled her.
So you're saying it might
be your sister? Maybe.
It was just a feeling I had.
But also, it had a strange
reaction when it saw my face.
Hmm.
Well, it did say something about
searching for a little brother.
I'm betting that just triggered
memories of your sister.
Besides, it told us that its brother is
supposedly the most handsome man ever.
And, well...
Yeah, true.
That doesn't describe me at all.
It was a ridiculous thought.
In any case, no ordinary human
could ever be that strong.
In addition, nobody's ever heard
of a human becoming a Shuki before.
We're most certainly bound
to cross paths again.
because we won't stop looking
until we find them. Right.
It's weird how excited you
seem about getting stepped on.
I mean, the view is nice from down here.
God damn it.
Miss Kyoka? No way!
Miss Kyoka seemed convinced that
it was a humanoid species of Shuki.
But if it really was my sister, why would
she be attacking the demon defense forces?
How has she stayed alive all this time?
And why is she working
with that horn monstrosity?
If we see them again, what should I...
Oh no! Mr. Yuki! Mr. Yuki!
Look, the pot is boiling over!
Ah!
I'm sorry, I was spacing out!
Kneel down here, please,
as your senpai Nei needs to take
care of some serious business!
What does she mean by that?
You expose this to danger,
and you must be punished!
Senpai, punch!
I'm sorry!
You had a big day out there fighting those
tough enemies to save Shushu from danger?
You're tired and your body
and brain need a rest.
I'm not the best cook, but
I can make simple meals.
Would you like me to handle dinner?
Wow, thank you.
It's all part of being a good senpai!
But I can't do it.
I'm good to cook.
I don't deserve such an amazing senpai.
Thank you.
Now, I would however take your help
plating the food, would you mind?
Just leave it out of me!
I can figure out whether she's my
sister or not the next time we meet.
For now, I gotta focus on work.
Crawling back here with injuries, really.
And I thought you were
above such disgraces, Alba.
What can I say?
I got taken by surprise.
They're all better.
It's perfect!
Thank you, Coco.
Hey!
That was Yuki, I'm sure of it.
But I don't know why
he looked like a Shuki?
An experiment by the demon defense force?
Or the ability of that woman riding him?
When did they start letting
guys in their organization?
But it was a nice reunion
Right?
Yuki the unicorn was crazy powerful if we
fight again you're already back in action.
Yep tip-top shape and thank you for
saving me when I was in trouble.
Of course don't mention it.
Why don't I let you return the
favor with a nice little back scrub?
Hey, enough with the jokes already!
You sure you want to turn around?
Because I'm completely naked.
So just quiet down and
let me wash your back.
Okay, big guy, here we go.
Is she actually naked back there?
I can't risk turning
around if that's true.
Shushu's pulling this
little prank because she
thinks I'm not the type of
guy who would turn around.
Or maybe that's just what
she wants me to think.
I hear that most people are
prone to playing it safe,
so confidently turning around and saying,
I knew you had a swimsuit
on, now get out of here,
would be the smart move in
order to teach her a lesson.
Here goes!
I wasn't bored yesterday, Shushu!
Ah!
Warm the air!
Away from me, woman!
Yuki just saw me naked!
Now my heart's racing!
Huh?
I guess you're ready to find me!
I'm interested!
Hold on!
I put up a sign that said Bath Occupied!
Well, you should have
made it more clear...
that it was a guy in the
bath, you perverted asshole!
Well, hello there.
Never a dull moment
with the seventh squad.
Intruder alert!
They're members of the sixth squad.
Oh.
I'm the commander, Miss Tenka Izumo.
I'm her second-in-command, Yachiho Azuma.
Azuma?
So you're the slave I've
heard so much about.
Well, anyway, go fetch Kyo for me.
Uh, you mean Miss Kyouka?
Sure, right away!
I'm going to take my power
to the power of my body.
I'm going to go two together.
I'm not a one-time.
I'm going to connect with you.
I'm going to take you to the train.
I'm not going to leave you.
Thank you.
T-Chat Maze Empire! Okay!
Today we're going to talk about my Peach
ability called Share Defined Promises.
Known as Clairvoyance, this
allows me to see places far away,
which I used to find
Shuki and Mato victims.
I can also share the POV of a
person who's touched me before.
It's valued by scouting teams.
There are some places I can't see,
like inside caves, and it's
pretty useless in combat.
But I believe that I have my own
role to play and always give my best.